

Naman Sharma

B.TECH COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEER

Contact

- +91-9174736520
- naman.sharma@avantika.edu.in
- @naman-github
- in linkedin.com/in/naman-ns23/

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- Python
- Django
- React Js
- API's
- HTML 5 / CSS 3
- Bootstrap
- Machine Learning
- Artificial Intelligence
- Database MySQL
- C/C++

About

My goal is to work to my full capacity in a demanding and dynamic atmosphere where I will have the opportunity to interact with a varied set of individuals while also increasing my professional abilities through learning and experience in order to advance my career.

Education History

Bachelors of Technology | CSE

2019-2023

Avantika University, MIT Pune Ujjain Campus

• CGPA 7.62 (Pursuing)

Current SGPA 8.9

XII Board (MPBSE)

Hansdas Academy, Indore

• Score - 81%

X Board (CBSE)

Indore Public School, Indore

• CGPA - 6.6

Work Experience

Ignite Solutions, Pune

(JAN 2023 - PRESENT)

Software Engineer Intern

- Complete Backend Development on Django.
- API Integration via Django Rest Framework.
- Frontend Development on React Js.
- Worked upon Internal Projects for the organization.
- Complete Software Development Life Cycle.

Cidrus Technologies, Banglore (JUN 2022 - AUG 2022)

Web Development and Research Intern

- Extensive research on competitor analysis.
- Framework identification.
- Worked on Front-End Development on Web-Application.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

- AgroAssay A Mobile Application based on Artificial Intelligence where the Assessment of grains been done based on quality parameters via image classification and prediction of price upon current market rates.
- AgroPro A <u>Machine Learning</u> Project where prediction services available to farmers integrated with both the technologies i.e., <u>Web Application</u> and Mobile Application.
- **AgroWeb** <u>Website</u> for selling Agriculture products Online and also information with dosing details.
- AgroPredict An <u>IOT application</u> can be used by farmers for predicting crops to be planted.
- AgriBook <u>Mobile application</u> for farmers to book the schedule for selling their crops at warehouses.
- ReMaSy Retail Management Software is the <u>Desktop Application</u> made by Qt Creator.

Certifications

- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp - Udemy
- Python Programming Coursera
- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage
- Diploma in Agri Business Pioneer Institute of Professional Studies, Indore

Other Area of Interests

- Community Involvement
- Travelling
- Entrepreneurship
- Gaming e-sports
- Business Handling
- Photography
- Music Listening